optionsuniversity.com 2015-03-17

# PRIVACY POLICY - Options University

**Last Updated: March 8, 2012**

Options University strives to offer its visitors the many advantages of Internet technology and to provide an interactive and personalized experience. We will use Personally Identifiable Information (including information such as your name, e-mail address, street address, telephone number) subject to the terms of this privacy policy.

_[](http://clicktoverify.truste.com/pvr.php?page=validate&url=www.optionsuniversity.com&sealid=101)Options University, LLC is a Participant in the TRUSTe Privacy Seal Program. TRUSTe is an independent organization whose mission is to advance privacy and trust in the networked world. As this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices monitored for compliance by TRUSTe._

_If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact us at[support@optionsuniversity.com](mailto:support@optionsuniversity.com). If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry, or if your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe at[http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint&url](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint&url) TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve your concerns._

The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, and does not cover information that may be collected through software downloaded from the site.

We will never sell, barter, or rent your email address to any third party except as described in this privacy policy.  
(See “Customer Service” section below.)

**How we gather information from users**

How we collect and store information including email address depends on the page you are visiting, the activities in which you elect to participate and the services provided. For example, you may be asked to provide information including email address when you register for access to certain portions of our site or request certain features, such as newsletters or when you make a purchase. You may provide information when you participate in sweepstakes and contests, message boards and chat rooms, and other interactive areas of our site.

**Registration**  
In order to use this Web site, you must first complete the registration form. During registration, you are required to give contact information, such as name and email address. We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest.

Please see “Communications from the Site” section.

Options University, LLC is the sole owner of the information collected onhttp://www.optionsuniversity.com. Options University, LLC, collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on the OU Web site.

**Orders**  
If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date).

We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

Please see “Communications from the Site” section.

**Surveys or Contests**  
From time-to-time, we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name, email address, and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code).

We use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes, to help improve the user experience on the site (in the case of anonymous information collected in surveys), or to send participants an email newsletter or free CD.

**Testimonials  
**We receive permission to post written and video testimonials prior to posting to our site.

**Co-branded sites**

We do not currently ‘Co-Brand’ although we do have several partnerships operating under the Options University brand including Options University Strategist ([www.OptionsUniversityStrategist.com](http://www.optionsuniversitystrategist.com/)) and OU Forex Trader ([www.OUForexTrader.com](http://www.ouforextrader.com/)) that we sometimes send promotional material, but these emails come from Options University directly and no personal information is otherwise ‘shared’. You can opt-out of receiving any promotional emails sent by Options University by following the unsubscribe information included in each promotional email.

We also have a ‘Coaching’ program through a third party service, Beacon Learning Group (BLG), in which certain customer data is shared for contacting customers on our behalf, to sell personal coaching programs, but under a strict non-solicitation and non-disclosure agreement between both parties that prohibits BLG from selling, sharing, or otherwise using this personal information for anything besides Options University coaching services. BLG is a service provider for Options University and will not contact customers for their own marketing purposes.

Like most Web sites, OptionsUniversity.com also collects information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be transparent to our visitors. For example, we may log the name of your Internet Service Provider or use cookie technology to recognize you and hold information from your visit. Among other things, the cookie may store your user name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you visit, or may control the number of times you encounter a particular advertisement while visiting our site. For these purposes our cookies are tied to your personally identifiable information.

While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may use cookies or other technology such as Web beacons to attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about you. For example, some of our advertising is served by third parties and may include cookies and Web beacons that enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before. We have no access or control of these types of third party tracking technologies.

Other features available on our site may offer services operated by third parties and may use cookies or other technology to gather information. OptionsUniversity.com does not control the use of this technology by third parties or the resulting information, and is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties. They may use technologies in our emails for tracking purposes.

As we adopt additional technology, we may also gather information through other means and we will disclose these new technologies as we adopt them as they relate to privacy and give you choice as to this new type of type of information collection IF it is a material change to our privacy policy. . In certain cases, you can choose not to provide us with information, for example by setting your browser to refuse to accept cookies, but if you do you may be unable to access certain portions of the site or may be asked to re-enter your user name and password, and we may not be able to customize the site’s features according to your preferences.

**What we do with the information we collect**

Like other Web publishers, we collect information to enhance your visit and deliver more individualized content and advertising. We respect your privacy and do not share your information with anyone except as described in this privacy statement.

Aggregated Information (information that does not personally identify you) may be used in many ways. For example, we may combine information about your usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to help enhance our site and services (e.g., to learn which pages are visited most or what features are most attractive). Aggregated Information may occasionally be shared with our advertisers and business partners. Again, this information does not include any Personally Identifiable Information about you or allow anyone to identify you individually.

We use Personally Identifiable Information collected on OptionsUniversity.com to communicate with you about your registration and customization preferences; our Terms of Service and privacy policy; services and products offered by OptionsUniversity.com and other topics we think you might find of interest.

**Communications from the Site**

**Special Offers and Updates**  
We will occasionally send you information on products, services, special deals, promotions, classes and webinars. You can sign up for these emails from us on our registration page.

Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. Please see the “Choice and Opt-out.”

**Newsletters**  
If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email or mailing address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe. Please see the “Choice and Opt-out” section.

**Service-related Announcements**  
We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email.

Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account. You may opt-out of these communications. Please see “Choice and Opt-out.”

**Customer Service**  
Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes.

Personally Identifiable Information collected by OptionsUniversity.com may also be used for other purposes, including but not limited to site administration, troubleshooting, processing of e-commerce transactions, administration of sweepstakes and contests, and other communications with you. Certain third parties who provide technical support for the operation of our site (our Web hosting and Email Service providers for example) may access such information. We will use your information only, as permitted by law and to provide services on our behalf. They may not use your personally identifiable information for their own promotional purposes.

In addition, from time to time as we continue to develop our business, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred assets. We may also disclose your information in response to a court order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do so by law, in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us, and/or to law enforcement authorities whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary. Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.

**Choice/Opt-out**

We provide you the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on our Thank You page.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at [support@OptionsUniversity.com](mailto:support@OptionsUniversity.com) We offer an opportunity to opt-out of certain communications, such as emails, at the bottom of the page, or you may contact us at 1-866-561-8227, [support@OptionsUniversity.com](mailto:support@OptionsUniversity.com) or 925 S. Federal Highway, Suite 510, Boca Raton, FL 33432 to opt-out.]

You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party.

**Access to Personally Identifiable Information**

If your personally identifiable information including email address changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or by making the change on our member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at [support@OptionsUniversity.com](mailto:support@OptionsUniversity.com) or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed above.

**Affiliated sites, linked sites and advertisements**

OptionsUniversity.com expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame on a OptionsUniversity.com page, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party.

Also, through OptionsUniversity.com you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, Web sites, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. OptionsUniversity.com is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party.

You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on our blog, message boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of OptionsUniversity.com and this policy.

**Security**

The security of your personal information including your email address is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means, such as a double firewall and Spam filtering, to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at support@OptionsUniversity.com

**Children**

OptionsUniversity.com does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under 13 . If we discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe, OptionsUniversity.com has any information from or about anyone under 13, please contact us at the address listed below.

**Contacting Us**

We can be reached by contacting:

OptionsUniversity.com  
925 S. Federal Highway  
Suite 510  
Boca Raton, FL  
33432  
Email: [support@OptionsUniversity.com](mailto:support@OptionsUniversity.com)

**Changes to this Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy or email practices, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy including our email practices, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

Copyright 2009 – 2012 All Rights Reserved
